Guide to the Creative Time Archive 1973-2006 MSS.179
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V: Video and Film
  - Subseries A: Video Recordings - Access Copies
    - The Art Guys, CBS [Press], [1998] (Case 179.0583)
      Duration: 00:10:00
    - "F.R.E.D." Projections, Fall 1999 (shot by Roberto Guerra) (Case 179.0625)
      Original Format: MiniDV
    - Art in the Anchorage - "Loud and Unhinged" (fashion video looped) 5/18/99, 1999 (Case 179.0298)
      Duration: 02:10:00
    - Art in the Anchorage - "Loud and Unhinged" (film video looped) 5/18/99, 1999 (Case 179.0300)
      Duration: 02:00:00
    - Art in the Anchorage - "Loud and Unhinged", [1999] (Case 179.0126)
    - Courtney Harmel, Brooklyn Library Projections, 11/6/99 (Tape 1), 1999 (Case 179.0194)
    - Standard and Poor, Carpet Rollers, Park Restaurant, 2/2/99, 1999 (Case 179.0250)
    - The Art Guys, Fashion TV [Press], 1999 (Case 179.0581)
    - The 59th Minute - Genevieve Cadieux, "Portrait", 1999-2000 (Case 179.0280)
    - [Art in the Anchorage] - Granular Synthesis, "Noise Gate" (Prod. Footage), [2000] (Case 179.0188)
    - "Tibor in Orbit", Times Square, May-June, 2000 (Case 179.0276)
    - Bus Tour, 9/27/00, 2000 (Case 179.0292)
    - Chris Doyle, "Leap", 2000 (Case 179.0455)
      Duration: 00:11:00
    - Chris Doyle, "Leap", Apr 27-30, 2000 (Case 179.0449)
      Duration: 00:04:00
    - Chris Doyle, "Leap" (Demo), [2000] (Case 179.0451)
    - "Leap", [2000] (Case 179.0515)
    - "Leap", Dec[ember], [2000] (Case 179.0453)
    - "Leap", Interviews, [2000] (Case 179.0457)
      Duration: 00:33:00
    - The 59th Minute - "Tibor in Orbit", 4/4/00, 2000 (Case 179.0352)
    - "Leap", "Tribute in Light", "Tap", "59th Minute" (show reel), [2000-2002] (Case 179.0419)
    - Art in the Anchorage - "Massless Medium: Explorations Sensory Immersion", 2001 (Case 179.0172)
    - Hans Haacke, May 12, 2001 (Case 179.0246)
    - Music in the Anchorage - 6/21/01 (rough footage), 2001 (Case 179.0647)
    - [Music in the Anchorage] - Porter Ricks, SND, 6/28 (#3), [2001] (Case 179.0619)
      Duration: 00:57:00
    - [Music in the Anchorage] - Porter Ricks, Thomas Heckman, 6/28 (#4), [2001] (Case 179.0621)
    - [Music in the Anchorage] 6/28 #3, [2001] (Case 179.0623)
    - Noam Toran, "Object for Lonely Men", Blur, 2001 (Case 179.0559)
    - Rachel Stevens, NAAMP Portfolio Presentation, 12/01, 2001 (Case 179.0429)
    - The 59th Minute - Bruce and Norman Yonemoto, "ahistory", Oct 19-Nov 30, 2001 (Case 179.0348)
    - The 59th Minute - Gary Hill, Michael Snow, Mary Lucier, "Fast Forward", 12/2/2001-1/27/02 (Case 179.0370)
    - The 59th Minute - Marco Brambilla, "Superstar", Feb 28-Apr 15, 2001 (Case 179.0354)
    - The 59th Minute - Marco Brambilla, "Superstar"; Fischli and Weiss, "Cat Drinking Milk"; William Kentridge, "Shadow", 2001 (Case 179.0258)
    - The 59th Minute - Michael Snow, "Fridge", 2001 (Case 179.0479)
    - "Out of the Ashes", "Towers of Light", Dateline, 10/21/01 [Press], 2001 (Case 179.0493)
    - "Out of the Ashes", Dateline, 10/21/01 [Press], 2001 (Case 179.0288)
    - The 59th Minute - Fischli and Weiss, "Cat Drinking Milk"; William Kentridge, "Shadows"; Bruce and Norman Yonemoto, "ahistory"; Jeff Gibson, "Viralysis"; Gary Hill, "Liminal Object"; Mary Lucier, "Monarch"; Michael Snow, "Fridge"; Genevieve Cadieux, "Portrait", [2001] (Case 179.0481)
    - Memorials, CBS Evening News, 12/11/01 [Press], 2001 (Case 179.0282)
    - "Tribute in Light" press conference, 3/6/02 (part 1 of 2) [Press], 2002 (Case 179.0425)
    - "Tribute in Light", Anne Pasternak, Pure Oxygen, 3/12/02 [Press], 2002 (Case 179.0551)
    - "Tribute in Light", Nippon Television, Tokyo, 3/9/02 [Press], 2002 (Case 179.0423)
    - "Tribute in Light", Nippon Television, Tokyo, 3/9/02 [Press], 2002 (Case 179.0547)
    - "Tribute in Light", Press Conference (tape 2 of 2) [Press], 2002 (Case 179.0549)
    - "Tribute in Light", Pure Oxygen, 4/10/02 (Segment B) [Press], 2002 (Case 179.0427)
    - "Tribute in Light", CNN, Towers of Light [Press], [2002] (Case 179.0545)
    - "Tribute in Light", Illumina TV, ArtsWorld [Press], [2002] (Case 179.0495)
    - "Tribute in Light", NY One [Press], [2002] (Case 179.0497)
      Format: DVD-R,
    - "Tribute in Light", Towers of Light, Proun Space Studio, [2002] (Case 179.0499)
    - Therese Cafaro, Jayson Haedrich, "Tribute: A Documentary", [2002] (Case 179.0421)
    - Everton Sylvester, Skylight Gallery, 9/5/02 (Tape 2), 2002 (Case 179.0154)
    - Everton Sylvester, Skylight Gallery, 9/5/02 (Tape 4), 2002 (Case 179.0166)
    - Everton Sylvester, 9/5/02 (tape 1), 2002 (Case 179.0641)
    - Everton Sylvester, 9/5/02 (tape 3), 2002 (Case 179.0631)
    - Gabri SI High School 9/13/02 (2 of 2), 2002 (Case 179.0615)
    - Gabri SI High School, 9/13/02 (1 of 2), 2002 (Case 179.0649)
      Duration: 00:39:00
    - Holiday Light Show - Grand Central Project, Comp Reel, [2002] (Case 179.0286)
    - James Buckhouse, Holly Brubach, "Tap" - Tech TV (30 second spot), 6/12/2002 [Press] (Case 179.0284)
    - "Sonic Garden", NY Tonight [Press], [2002] (Case 179.0296)
    - Stephanie Simon, "Poster Project", 2/02, 2002 (Case 179.0268)
    - Toshi, 8/28/02 (1 of 2), 2002 (Case 179.0633)
    - Toshi, 8/28/02 (2 of 2), 2002 (Case 179.0617)
    - William Wegman - [The 59th Minute] Fox Good Day Live, 11/18/02 [Press], 2002 (Case 179.0374)
    - Adelle Lutz, "The Peace Piece", [2003] (Case 179.0605)
    - Artist Roundtable (final group discussion), 8/5/03, 2003 (Case 179.0136)
    - Artist Roundtable (Vardit's Group), 8/5/03, 2003 (Case 179.0150)
    - Artists Roundtable, Vardit, [2003] (Case 179.0503)
    - Artist Roundtable, Carol's Group, 8/5/03, 2003 (Case 179.0639)
    - Cai Guo-Qiang, "Gunpowder", drawings at Grucci, 8/7/03, 2003 (Case 179.0635)
    - Cai Guo-Qiang, "Light Cycle", 2003 (Case 179.0274)
    - [Cai Guo-Qiang], "Light Cycle", "Aerial", [2003] (Case 179.0190)
    - Cai Guo-Qiang, "Light Cycle", [2003] (Case 179.0637)
    - Focus Group, 3/24/03 (1 of 2), 2003 (Case 179.0643)
    - Focus Group, 3/24/03 (2 of 2), 2003 (Case 179.0645)
    - The 59th Minute - Thomas Struth, 2003 (Case 179.0386)
    - [The 59th Minute] - Thomas Struth, "Video Portraits": Kim Heirston, Thomas Gutt, Anne Grefe, Rafael Hartmann, [2003] (Case 179.0607)
    - Thomas Struth Exhibit, German television, 2/4/03 [Press], 2003 (Case 179.0362)
    - CBS Sunday Morning, "Freedom of Expression", 7/4/04 [Press], 2004 (Case 179.0294)
    - Freedom of Expression [Monument], 11/04, 2004 (Case 179.0489)
    - Jenny Holzer, "For New York City" (1), 2004 (Case 179.0585)
    - Jenny Holzer, "For New York City" (2), 2004 (Case 179.0593)
    - Jenny Holzer, "For The City" (raw footage), [2004] (Case 179.0587)
    - "For New York City", '04, Xenon Projections at Bethesda Fountain, Central Park, 10/27/04 (tape 4), 2004 (Case 179.0591)
    - O and A [Sam Auinger and Bruce Odland], "Blue Moon", Stephanie Simon 5/04 [Press], 2004 (Case 179.0471)
    - The 59th Minute - "Dream Sequence", "Dwelling", "Mousetrap" 1/18/04, 2004 (Case 179.0308)
    - The 59th Minute - Carlos Amorales, "The Forest", 10/28/04, 2004 (Case 179.0310)
    - The 59th Minute - Gunther Selichar, [2004] (Case 179.0248)
    - The 59th Minute - Hiraki Sawa, "Dwelling"; Janaina Tschape, "Dream Sequence", Jan 21-May 16, 2004 (Case 179.0378)
    - The 59th Minute - Hiraki Sawa, "Dwelling"; Janaina Tschape, "Dream Sequence", Jan 21-May 16, 2004 (Case 179.0415)
    - The 59th Minute - [Carlos] Amorales, Televisa New York, [2004-2005] (Case 179.0483)
    - Anne Pasternak, Stephanie Simon, 2/05 [Press], 2005 (Case 179.0270)
    - Dreamland Artist Club - Stephanie Simon, 2005 (Case 179.0130)
    - Jenny Holzer, Bobst Library, NYU, 11/16/05, 2005 (Case 179.0589)
    - Jenny Holzer, Political Art (edit), Reuters, Fall 2005 (Case 179.0595)
    - Song Dong, "Evaporating Art", Reuters, 2005 (Case 179.0372)
    - "Living With AIDS: Seize Control of the FDA", Undated (Case 179.0523)
    - # 4, 6/28, Undated (Case 179.0146)
    - [unidentified], Undated (Case 179.0164)
      Duration: 00:47:00
    - [unidentified], Undated (Case 179.0555)
    - 1st Tape "R", Undated (Case 179.0200)
    - Ange Leccia, Undated (Case 179.0360)
    - Art on the Beach 1, Undated; ID: 179.0726 (Case 179.0726)
      Physical Characteristics and Techincal Requirements Note
    - Art on the Beach, Undated; ID: 179.0711 (Case 179.0711)
    - Art on the Beach / School of Hard Knocks, Undated; ID: 179.0708 (Case 179.0708)
    - 2 Art on the Beach School of Hard Knocks, Undated; ID: 179.0735 (Case 179.0735)
    - Art on the Beach (Creative Time Master), Undated; ID: 179.0702 (Case 179.0702)
    - Art on the Beach (tape 1), Undated (Case 179.0330)
    - Art on the Beach (tape 2, Kay Lynn), Undated (Case 179.0344)
    - Art on the Beach Kay Lynn 2, Undated; ID: 179.0729 (Case 179.0729)
    - Art on the Beach (tape 3, Kay Lynn), Undated (Case 179.0356)
    - Art on the Beach Kay Lynn 3, Undated; ID: 179.0732 (Case 179.0732)
    - Art on the Beach (tape 5), Undated (Case 179.0376)
    - Bill Shannon, Axis Dance and Solo, Undated (Case 179.0368)
    - Burlesque Video, 2 Versions, Undated (Case 179.0433)
    - Dreamland Artist Club, Undated (Case 179.0132)
    - Fair and Balanced News/ Freedom, Undated (Case 179.0525)
      Duration: [1]--00:02:00 [2]--00:06:00 [3]--00:51:00
    - Grand Central Installation, Undated (Case 179.0138)
    - Grand Central Installation, Undated (Case 179.0198)
      Duration: 01:07:00
    - Grand Central Installation, Undated (Case 179.0627)
      Duration: 01:02:00
    - Granular Synthesis, Undated (Case 179.0174)
    - Kathy Brew, Roberto Guerra, DNAID, Undated (Case 179.0272)
    - Marjetica Potrc, "Borders" (Tape 1), Undated (Case 179.0180)
    - Marjetica Potrc, "Borders" (tape 2, beginning of general discussion), Undated (Case 179.0629)
      Duration: 01:21:00
    - Peter Freusen Descartes Video, Undated; ID: 179.0774 (Case 179.0774)
    - Ringside, Undated; ID: 179.0696 (Case 179.0696)
    - Susan Cianciolo, "Diadel", Undated (Case 179.0182)
    - William Kentridge, Undated (Case 179.0260)
    - Zhang Huan, Undated (Case 179.0128)
    - Masstransiscope by Bill Brand, 1980; ID: 179.0776 (Case 179.0776)
      Original Format: Unknown
  - Subseries B: Video Recordings - Originals
    - Liz Phillips, Installations Documentary Compilation, 1970-1999 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0675)
      Format: Format: VHS
      Duration: [25 min.]
    - Big Apple Minute, Ruckus Manhattan [Press], 1976 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0311)
      Format: Format: 3/4" video cassette
    - Art on the Beach (aerial videotaping by Joe Kos), 1978 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0323)
      Format: 3/4" video cassette
    - Art on the Beach (video by Joe Kos), 1978 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0277)
    - [Custom and Culture] - Jim Pomeroy, 5/31/79, 1979 (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0695)
      Format: Format: Betamax
      Duration: [Unknown]
    - [Custom and Culture] - Kenneth Rinker, Dancers, 5/20/79, 1979 (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0694)
    - [Custom and Culture] - Stuart Sherman, 6/8/79; Laurie Anderson and Peter Gordon, 6/14/79, 1979 (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0696)
    - SRL [Survival Research Laboratories], TV Spots, 6/86, 6/81, 9/89, 11/83 [Press], 1981, 1983, 1986, 1989 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0556)
      Format: VHS
    - Alice Farley, "The Water Garden" - Cooper-Hewitt Museum, 8/82, 1982 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0237)
    - Art on the Beach - Danny McCusker, "Art in the Anchorage with Warhol", "Big Apple Minutes", 1982 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0239)
    - Tannis Hugill, "Hanging Woman", "Flagella: A Space Probe", 1982-1984 (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0687)
      Format: 3/4" Umatic
    - Art in the Anchorage - Station House Opera, "Drunken Madness", 1983 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0241)
    - Art on the Beach - Live at 5, 5/13/83 [Press], 1983 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0476)
    - Magnificent Force, Panache, Sesame St., 9/1983 (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0690)
    - Art on the Beach - 1984 highlights (Dan Freel, edited master 2/8/85) (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0412)
    - Art on the Beach - MTV, 7/7/84-9/16/84 [Press], 1984 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0651)
    - Art on the Beach (highlight reel), 1984 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0315)
    - Art in the Anchorage - "The Memory Theater of Giulio Camillo", 1985 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0203)
    - Art on the Beach - Yoshiko Chuma, Lenny Pickett, Fred Wilson, 1985 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0321)
    - Art on the Beach - "School of Hard Knocks" (tape 2), [1985] (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0331)
    - Art on the Beach - "School of Hard Knocks" (tape 3), [1985] (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0319)
    - Art on the Beach - "School of Hard Knocks" (tape 7), [1985] (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0317)
    - Art on the Beach - Yoshiko Chuma, "School of Hard Knocks", [1985] (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0313)
    - Art on the Beach (CBC Master #1), 1985 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0325)
    - Art on the Beach (CBC Master #2), 1985 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0327)
    - Marianne Goldberg, "Environs" (excerpts), 1985 (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0689)
    - Subway Art, Live From Underground, 9/29/85 (2), 1985 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0652)
    - Subway Art, Live From Underground (3), [1985] (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0653)
    - Subway Art, Live From Underground, 9/29/85 (4), 1985 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0654)
    - Subway Art, Live From Underground, 9/29/85-9/30/85 (5), 1985 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0655)
    - Subway Art, Live From Underground, 9/29/85 (7), 1985 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0656)
    - Subway Art (8), [1985] (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0657)
    - Subway Art (9), [1985] (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0658)
    - Subway Art (10), [1985] (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0659)
    - [Subway Art] (11), [1985] (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0660)
    - Survival Research Laboratories, "Virtues of Negative Fascination", 1985-1986 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0677)
      Duration: [80 min.]
    - Survival Research Laboratories (Mark Pauline, Matt Heckert, Eric Werner), "The Virtues of Negative Fascination", [1985-1986] (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0598)
    - Art in the Anchorage - John Kelly, 6/22/87, 1987 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0500)
    - Art on the Beach (opening) - Mark Antrobus, "Mud People", 1987 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0253)
    - Gretchen Langheld, Creative Time Benefit, 6/30/87, 1987 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0402)
    - John Torreano, Creative Time Benefit, 6/10/87, 1987 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0468)
    - Performance in the Park - Clarice Marshall, 1987 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0289)
    - SRL [Survival Research Laboratories], CNN, 8/13/87 (Filmed at Stanford Conference on Design, July 1987) [Press] (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0596)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Contraband, Evol, 1988 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0147)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Scott Sherk, Joel Sanders, Ed Tomney, Brigid Kennedy, 1988 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0209)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Station House Opera (long shot from front), 1988 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0207)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Station House Opera, "Piranesi in NY", 1988 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0195)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Station House Opera, "Piranesi in NY" (complete performance), 1988 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0211)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Station House Opera, "Piranesi in NY" (NTSC Dub), 1988 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0213)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Station House Opera, 6/14/88 (ledge, stage left, cut-aways), 1988 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0404)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Station House Opera, 6/16/88 (3rd row, tight in), 1988 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0406)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Station House Opera, 6/18/88 (3rd Row Wide Shot), 1988 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0151)
    - Marcos Kurtycz, "Organikwars" 12/8/88-12/10/88; "Organrites" 12/8/88; "One Dos Tres O!" 12/9/88; "Clavarte" 12/10/88, 1988 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0458)
    - SRL [Survival Research Laboratories], Shea Stadium 5/19/88; CBS News 5/17/88 [Press] (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0464)
    - Survival Research [Laboratories], [1988] (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0602)
    - Survival Research Laboratories, [1988] (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0552)
    - Tony Fisher, Steven Ausbury, "The Lost Opera", 1988 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0462)
    - Dumb Type, "pH" 1990, "Pleasure Life" 1988, 1988, 1990 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0540)
    - Merry Conway, Noni Pratt, "As a Dream That Vanishes" 1991; "In the Eye of the Beholder" 1988, 1988, 1991 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0460)
    - "Desire Borne", 1989 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0381)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Jessie Jane Lewis, "Blind Ally", 6/22/89, 1989 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0177)
    - Leni Schwendinger, "Light Site-ings", 11/1/89, 1989 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0265)
    - Mark Pauline, 1989 Sculpture Grant Award Exhibition, San Francisco Artspace, July 11-Aug 19, 1989 (Dir. Jonathan Reiss and Leslie Asako Gladsjo) (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0600)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Karen Finley, "3 Parables and 2 Testimonies", 9/28/90, 1990 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0191)
    - HIV TV, Swarthmore College, 12/16/90, 1990 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0520)
    - John Kelly, "Love of a Poet", 10/19/90 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0436)
    - Kit-Yin Snyder, Enrico IV Set/Installation - Creative Media Conc., 9/25/90, 1990 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0434)
    - The Bowery Concert, 9/15/90 (4 PM show), 1990 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0416)
    - Cai Guo-Qiang, "Explosion Projects", 1990-2002 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0663)
    - "Clean Needles Save Lives", [1991] (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0526)
    - "Needle Exchange" (without credits), [1991] (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0528)
    - Dumb Type, "pH", Kyoto Municipal Museum of the Arts, Institute Contemporary Arts, Nagoya, Spring 1991 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0536)
    - Dumb Type, "pH", [1991] (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0538)
    - Dumb Type, "pH", [1991] (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0542)
    - Fear of Disclosure - Ellen Spiro, Marina Alvarez, "(In)Visible Women", [1991] (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0444)
    - Jordi Torrent, "Honeymoon", 1991 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0438)
    - Antoni Miraldi, "Honeymoon Project" (cued for 10 minute viewing segment, parts I and II), [1991] (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0141)
    - La Fura Dels Baus, "Suz/O/Suz", 4/1/91, 1991 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0185)
    - "Transitions Inc.", 5/9/92, 1992 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0440)
    - Fear of Disclosure - Marlon Riggs, "Non, Je Ne Regrette Rien", 1992 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0446)
    - Fear of Disclosure - Marlon Riggs, "Non, Je Ne Regrette Rien", [1992] (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0668)
      Duration: [37 min.]
    - Jordi Torrent, "Monuments in Love", 1992 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0139)
    - Maria Perez, "Safersister" Public Service Announcements (in English and Spanish), [1992] (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0682)
    - "Patina Du Prey's Memorial Dress", Hunter Reynolds, ICA Boston, 1993 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0510)
    - "We Interrupt This Program" (Dir. Mary Ellen Strom, Prod. Barbara L. Tsumagari), 1993 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0674)
    - 42nd Street Art Project - Interviews, 1993 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0486)
    - 42nd Street Art Project - News All Evening NY 1 6/21/93; News All Morning NY 1 7/30/93; Good Day NY 7/6/93; Daybreak CNN 7/10/93; Channel 9 News 8/2/93; MTV News 8/11/93; NY Views 8/14/93 [Press], 1993 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0472)
    - 42nd Street Art Project - TV coverage, interviews [Press], 1993 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0397)
    - 42nd Street Art Project - TV coverage, interviews [Press], 1993 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0399)
      Duration: [90 min.]
    - 42nd Street Art Project - TV coverage, interviews [Press], 1993 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0400)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Elizabeth Streb, Dyke TV, Episode 19, 1993 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0504)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Elizabeth Streb, Ringside, "Kid Action", 1993 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0243)
    - Debra Levine, "Hairy Tales", [1993] (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0442)
    - Dyke TV Arts Compilation, 1993 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0508)
    - Dyke TV, Episodes 1 and 3, 1993 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0506)
    - Elizabeth Streb, "Ringside" Choreography (excerpts), 1993 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0681)
    - Glenn Belverio, "Two Spirits Speak Out", 1993 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0263)
    - Nelson Rodriguez, "HIV: A Home Video" (Draft #2), "13 Years" (Draft #3), "HIV: A Home Video" (Draft #4), 1993 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0518)
    - Thomas Allen Harris, "Heaven Earth and Hell", 1993 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0365)
    - Toni Dove, "Mesmer, Secrets of the Human Frame", [1993] (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0670)
      Duration: [12 min.]
    - 20 Years of Art in Unexpected Places, Dyke TV, 7/94, 1994 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0357)
    - 20 Years of Art in Unexpected Places, Dyke TV, 7/94, 1994 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0430)
    - 20th Anniversary celebration (tape 1), 1994 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0391)
      Format: HI 8
    - 20th Anniversary Celebration (tape 2), 1994 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0393)
    - 20th Anniversary Celebration, 7/7/94 (tape 1 of 2), 1994 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0608)
    - 20th Anniversary Celebration, 7/7/94 (tape 2 of 2), 1994 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0363)
    - 20th Anniversary Celebration, 7/7/94 (tape 3), 1994 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0395)
    - Anniversary Party Interviews, [1994] (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0484)
    - 42nd Street Art Project - PBS Video, MacNeil Lehrer News Hour, 9/23/94 [Press], 1994 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0474)
    - Dyke TV, Best of Winter '94, 1994 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0516)
    - Martha Wilson, Joyce Scott, Blondell Cummings, Reno, Carnival Knowledge, "Body Politics", 2/14/94, 1994 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0512)
    - Martha Wilson, Mary Ellen Strom, Peggy Pettitt, Holly Hughes, "Body Politics", 2/15/94, 1994 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0383)
    - Rebecca Bollinger, "Alphabetically Sorted", 1994 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0201)
    - Use Mass Transit - Hey Bozo! TV Coverage [Press], [1994] (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0251)
    - Relax, Fly Mass Transit, 1995 (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0697)
      Format: 5.25" Removable Hard Disk Cartridge
    - Thomas Allen Harris, "Vintage: Families of Value" documentary, 1995 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0255)
    - VAPP 1995 Application - Gretchen Bender, "Still/Here", "Total Recall"; Ron Kuivila, "VR on $5/Day; Frank Mann, "A Timely Existence"; Grahame Weinbren: "Sonata", "The Erl King" (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0261)
    - Art in the Anchorage - EAR, Harmony Rockets, 1996 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0215)
    - D.A. Therrien, "Pandaemonium", BBC 1996 [Press] (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0693)
    - Music in the Anchorage (demo reel), 1996 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0155)
    - Paco Cao, "Rent A Body", Carol and Marylyn TV Talk Show, [1996] (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0466)
    - Pierrick Sorin, "A Very Full Life", et. al., [1996] (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0157)
    - Pierrick Sorin, "C'est Mignon toutsa", [1996] (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0143)
      Duration: [45 min.]
    - Susan Cianciolo, "Run 3 Fashion Show", 1996 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0679)
    - Adrianne Wortzel, "Technoseduction Exhibition", "My Robotic", "The Ship's Detective" projection installation, [1997] (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0159)
    - Ange Leccia, "Sabatina", 1997 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0410)
    - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage - Rough Footage, 9/11/97, 1997 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0169)
    - Chrysanne Stathacos, "India 2026", "The Wish Machine", [1997] (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0683)
    - Magali Claude, "Tiems. Toi droit", "Les Gestes du Travail", "La Chora. Les rumours", 1997 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0490)
    - "ATM Art" (5/98), "Gesture as Value" (6/98), BBC [Press], 1998 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0303)
    - Ange Leccia, "ISA", 1998 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0379)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Detroit Techno, 1998 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0161)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Standard and Poor, "Big Night Out", 6/18/98, 1998 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0167)
    - Jerelyn Hanrahan, "Gesture as Value", [1998] (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0305)